<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetup on LeedsDevops</title>
    <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/tags/meetup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetup on LeedsDevops</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code released under the Apache 2.0 license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 15:43:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/tags/meetup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 24th November 2015 at The ODI Node in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2015-11-03-meetup-tuesday-24th-november-2015-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 15:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2015-11-03-meetup-tuesday-24th-november-2015-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Following the success of our October meetup and TechnloogyUG event we return to out spiritual home of the Leeds ODI node on Tuesday 24th November 2015 for the final Devops get together of the year…
6:45 - 7:15 : Grab a beer, have a natter.7:15 - 7:30 : Group updates/news/announcements7:30 - 8:00 : Verifying deployments and testing infrastructure with conn-check - Wes Mason8:00 - 8:15 : Intermission8:15 - 9:00 : Re:invent + Tech Deepdive on Lambda and Containers - Ian Massingham9:00 - late : Decamp to the WardrobeIt&#39;s great to welcome back to LeedsDevops two of our favourite speakers and local tech gurus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 29th September 2015 at The ODI Node in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2015-08-31-meetup-tuesday-29th-september-2015-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 19:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2015-08-31-meetup-tuesday-29th-september-2015-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>After a well deserved summer break we&#39;re back at the Leeds ODI node on Tuesday 29th September 2015 for a cracker of a Devops evening...
6:45 - 7:15 : Grab a beer, have a natter. 7:15 - 7:30 : Group updates/news/announcements 7:30 - 8:00 : Say Goodbye to Pet Projects - Tom Walton 8:00 - 8:15 : Intermission 8:15 - 9:00 : ChatOps with Hubot - Lorna Mitchell 9:00 - late : Decamp to the Wardrobe After much heranging and blatant pestering we&#39;ve at last persuaded Tom Walton from Infinity Works to come and talk about adopting DevOps culture with his talk &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 19th May 2015 at The ODI Node in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2015-04-26-meetup-tuesday-19th-may-2015-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 18:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2015-04-26-meetup-tuesday-19th-may-2015-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 19th May 2015 sees us return to the Open Data Institute Leeds Node. After last times Panel format we&amp;rsquo;re back to to our usual running order of two fantastic speakers&amp;hellip;
6:45 - 7:15 : Grab a beer, have a natter.7:15 - 7:30 : Group updates/news/announcements7:30 - 8:00 : Delivering microservices in the cloud8:00 - 8:15 : Intermission8:15 - 9:00 : DevopsDays Paris Recap9:00 - late : Decamp to the WardrobeAndrew Norman is a Principal Architect at BJSS and will speaking about &amp;ldquo;Delivering microservices in the cloud&amp;rdquo; - Andrew will be presenting a case study on how BJSS delivered a solution, presenting it&amp;rsquo;s architecture, CI, infrastructure and monitoring - the talk covers many hot topics in the devops community (microservices, AWS, containers, jenkins, puppet, sensu and graphite) definitely not one to be missed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 14th October 2014 at The Adelphi in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-09-29-meetup-tuesday-14th-october-2014-at-the-adelphi-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-09-29-meetup-tuesday-14th-october-2014-at-the-adelphi-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Ladies and Gentlemen, the 14th October is not only the date of our next meetup, but is exactly one year to the day since we had our Inaugural meetup to discuss if the group was worth forming. It was a small affair with about 6 of us upstairs at the Brewery Tap (infact we shared the room with Leeds Alopicia society separated by only a curtain). There was a general consensus that the group had a future, we then drank beer, and talked about devops, file systems and quadcopters, the rest is history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 16th September 2014 at The Salem Chapel in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-26-meetup-tuesday-16th-september-2014-at-the-salem-chapel-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-26-meetup-tuesday-16th-september-2014-at-the-salem-chapel-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Our next Meetup will take place on the 16th September at AQL Salem Chapel. We have two great speakers, firstly we have Sriram Rajan from Rackspace, we asked you what you wanted him to talk about and&amp;hellip;
You chose Ansible, big thanks to Sriram for letting us&amp;nbsp;throw it open to a vote so many great topics to choose from.
We also have Gemma Cameron and James Jefferies coming to talk about &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s next for DevOps?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Pictures From Our Meetup 12/08/14</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-17-a-few-pictures-from-our-meetup-12-08-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-17-a-few-pictures-from-our-meetup-12-08-14/</guid>
      <description>It was the busiest meetup we&#39;ve had to date with some of the most thought provoking and insightful talks&amp;nbsp;too, here are a couple of snaps from the night:
The calm before the storm
Expectant crowd
&amp;nbsp;
Justin from Chef talks to us about Accelerating Devops in the Enterprise
&amp;nbsp;
The Journey to devops
Jon from Pitchero explains their infrastructure
A massive thanks to everyone who came down to the meetup, cracking talks from Justin and Jon, as always a big thanks to our sponsors AQL, Chef and Pitchero</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOLD OUT - Tuesday 12th August 2014 Meetup</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-06-sold-out-tuesday-12th-august-2014-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-06-sold-out-tuesday-12th-august-2014-meetup/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;ve shifted 80 tickets for our meet up at AQL on the 12th with Chef and Pichero and are now SOLD OUT, we&#39;re asking our friends at AQL nicely if we can increase capacity a teensy bit. We&#39;re also opening the doors at 6:45pm so people have a little more time to get a beer.In the meantime the waiting list is enabled at eventbrite so sign up and we&#39;ll release the tickets if places become available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Wednesday 2nd July 2014 at The Salem Chapel in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-06-18-meetup-wednesday-2nd-july-2014-at-the-salem-chapel-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2014 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-06-18-meetup-wednesday-2nd-july-2014-at-the-salem-chapel-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve managed to find a date and venue sandwiched between World Cup fixtures. Our next Devops meetup will take place at 7pm on Wednesday 2nd July at the home of AQL in Leeds&amp;rsquo; coolest venue The Salem Chapel
 
 We have two great speakers for you:
Peter Maude - CTO of Leeds Based Crisp Thinking, they provide a service that takes care of moderating and managing User Generated Content, enabling customers to focus on delivering a social experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 20th May 2014 at The ODI Node in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-05-05-meetup-tuesday-20th-may-2014-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-05-05-meetup-tuesday-20th-may-2014-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>This month we&#39;ll be at the Open Data Institute Leeds Node. Situated just around the corner from the BBC, Aagrah and the Wardrobe at the top of Munro House. We decide we should really get somewhere that had space for us all (last month at the Adelphi was a little too &#34;cosy&#34;). So we have a great venue with a nice big screen, plenty of seating and panic not - a bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leeds Devops Meetup 15/04/14</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-05-05-leeds-devops-meetup-150414-a-very-full-adelphi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-05-05-leeds-devops-meetup-150414-a-very-full-adelphi/</guid>
      <description>Leeds Devops Meetup 15/04/14 - a very full Adelphi in Leeds</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 15th April 2014 at The Adelphi Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-03-24-meetup-tuesday-15th-april-2014-at-the-adelphi-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 21:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-03-24-meetup-tuesday-15th-april-2014-at-the-adelphi-leeds/</guid>
      <description>The April 2014 meet up will take place at the Adelphi in Leeds on Tuesday 15th April at 7pm. Here&#39;s the programme for your delectation and delight: 7:00 - 7:20 : Grab a beer, say hello and scoff a chipy butty. 7:20 - 7:30 : Group updates/news/announcements from Andy Burgin 7:30 - 8:00 : Wes Mason &#34;Where Goombas Dare - Build pipelines, Release Engineering, and You!&#34; 8:00 - 8:15 : Intermission 8:15 - 9:00 : Ian Massingham &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 4th March 2014 at The Adelphi Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-02-16-meetup-tuesday-4th-march-2014-at-the-adelphi-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-02-16-meetup-tuesday-4th-march-2014-at-the-adelphi-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Following&amp;nbsp; the January meetup we&#39;re back , this time at The Adelphi in Leeds on Tuesday 4th March 2014 at 7pm, which means we can increase the capacity upto 40 people.As always we we&#39;ve some great speakers and if you&#39;d like to sponsor the event (venue, bar and food) then please let us know.
This month we have...
 Simon Davy will be talking to us about how Canonical use Juju to develop and deploy complex environments in production that provide services for Ubuntu users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 26th November 2013 at The Central Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-11-16-meetup-tuesday-26th-november-2013-at-the-central-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2013 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-11-16-meetup-tuesday-26th-november-2013-at-the-central-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Yes I know it&#39;s a bit short notice but we finally got something booked. Lets get together at The Central Leeds on Tuesday 26th November 2013 starting at 7pmThis is the plan...
 We&#39;ll start the evening with a quick recap of the groups aims and objectives Next Andy Burgin from MadeByPi will be talking about his recent outing to DevopsDays London, sharing his opinions on the talks and speakers whilst wearing his nice new T-Shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Meetup - Tuesday 26th November</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-11-14-second-meetup-tuesday-26th-november/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 08:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-11-14-second-meetup-tuesday-26th-november/</guid>
      <description>We decided to go ahead with the second meetup on Tuesday 26th November.
We still have some details&amp;nbsp;to sort out, such as venue, time and speaker - but we are on with that now and hope to have this nailed in the next&amp;nbsp;day or two.&amp;nbsp;Just wanted to let you all know so you could keep your diaries free!
More news soon.
&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes from Inaugural Meetup</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-11-02-notes-from-inaugural-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2013 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-11-02-notes-from-inaugural-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Brewery Tap Leeds - 14/10/13@7:00pm
The agenda for the evening was:
 Short presentation about the group and proposed ideas. Discussion on what the group should be representing. Ideas for future meetups including format and topics. Appeal for helpers, speakers, sponsors and publicity  Attendees from Label Media, Flo Design, Sky Bet, Brighthost, Canonical, Corecom, MadeByPi and others.Outcome
Group founder @andyburgin presented his view on what the group should be about and it&#39;s objectives, this was recived well and encouraged a discussion on who the group should be for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Inaugural Meeting 14/10/13 @ Brewery Tap Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-10-01-the-inaugural-meeting-14-10-13-brewery-tap-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-10-01-the-inaugural-meeting-14-10-13-brewery-tap-leeds/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s with great excitement we announce the inaugural meeting of LeedsDevops.
Here&#39;s a quick agenda....
 Short presentation about the group and proposed ideas. Disscusion on what the group should be representing. Ideas for future meetups including format and topics Appeal for helpers, speakers, sponsors and publicity  As this is the first meetup there&#39;s no &#34;Technical Presentation&#34; or &#34;Speaker&#34;, it&amp;rsquo;s much more informal getting the thing off the ground chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neighbours, everybody needs good Neighbours.</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-09-25-neighbours-everybody-needs-good-neighbours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2013 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2013-09-25-neighbours-everybody-needs-good-neighbours/</guid>
      <description>So with well over a hundred and thirty&amp;nbsp;twitter followers it&#39;s time to start thinking of our first meetup, So like a couple moving into a starter home, we should say hello to the neighbours....
 Leeds Php meet 3rd Monday of each month - http://leedsphp.org/ Leeds Ruby Thing meet the last Thursday of the month - http://lanyrd.com/guides/leeds-ruby-thing/ Node Up North - meet the last Wednesday of the month - http://www.meetup.com/NodeUpNorth/ Leeds JS seem to be hibernating at the moment - http://javascript-leeds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>