<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chef on LeedsDevops</title>
    <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/tags/chef/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chef on LeedsDevops</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Code released under the Apache 2.0 license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 09:32:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/tags/chef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Monday 18th February 2019 at The ODI Node in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2019-02-06-meetup-monday-18th-february-2019-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 09:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2019-02-06-meetup-monday-18th-february-2019-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Time for our second meetup of 2019 at The ODI Node in Leeds on Monday 18th February 2019:
 6:45 - 7:15 : Doors open, have a chat, make some new devops friends 7:15 - 7:25 : Group updates/news/announcements 7:25 - 8:05 : The Case Against Microservices 8:05 - 8:20 : Intermission 8:20 - 9:00 : Habitat 9:00 - late : Social  Our first speaker of the evening is Aled Sage who is VP Engineering at Cloudsoft and co-founder of Apache Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 31st January 2017 at The ODI Node in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2017-01-09-meetup-tuesday-31st-january-2017-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 19:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2017-01-09-meetup-tuesday-31st-january-2017-at-the-odi-node-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>Happy new year! it&#39;s time for the first devops get together of 2017 at the ODI Node in Leeds on Tuesday 31st January. We have a fantastic array of talks for you:
6:45 - 7:15 : Doors open, have a chat, make some new devops friends
7:15 - 7:30 : Group updates/news/announcements
7:30 - 8:05 :Lessons Learned From Continuous Delivery - Mandi Walls of Chef
8:05 - 8:20 : Intermission</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Pictures From Our Meetup 12/08/14</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-17-a-few-pictures-from-our-meetup-12-08-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-17-a-few-pictures-from-our-meetup-12-08-14/</guid>
      <description>It was the busiest meetup we&#39;ve had to date with some of the most thought provoking and insightful talks&amp;nbsp;too, here are a couple of snaps from the night:
The calm before the storm
Expectant crowd
&amp;nbsp;
Justin from Chef talks to us about Accelerating Devops in the Enterprise
&amp;nbsp;
The Journey to devops
Jon from Pitchero explains their infrastructure
A massive thanks to everyone who came down to the meetup, cracking talks from Justin and Jon, as always a big thanks to our sponsors AQL, Chef and Pitchero</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The £1000 Chef Fundamentals Workshop Giveaway</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-11-the-1000-chef-fundamentals-workshop-giveaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2014 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-08-11-the-1000-chef-fundamentals-workshop-giveaway/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re extremely flattered and excited that our friends at chef have donated a place on their upcoming Chef Fundamentals Workshop as a prize at our meetup tomorrow. The training is worth a &amp;pound;1000 and is two day instructor-taught training teaching you how to write infrastructure code in chef. Overview of Chef Workstation Setup Node Setup Dissecting your first Chef run Introducing the Node object Chef resources and recipes Attributes, templates, and cookbook dependencies Template variables, notifications, and controlling idempotency Recipe inclusion, data bags, and search roles Environments Using community cookbooks Further resources  More details can be found at http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetup - Tuesday 12th August 2014 at The Salem Chapel in Leeds</title>
      <link>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-07-16-meetup-tuesday-12th-august-2014-at-the-salem-chapel-in-leeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2014 20:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.leedsdevops.org.uk/post/2014-07-16-meetup-tuesday-12th-august-2014-at-the-salem-chapel-in-leeds/</guid>
      <description>It may be a lazy summers day but we&amp;rsquo;ve pulled together a cracker of an evening for you. Our next Devops meetup will take place at 6:45pm on Tuesday 12th August thanks to the generosity of our friends AQL at the Salem Chapel.
We&amp;rsquo;ve really done ourselves proud and got a couple of top notch speakers:
Fresh from ChefConf Justin Arbuckle the VP EMEA &amp;amp; Chief Enterprise Architect Chef (formally Opscode) will be in attendance to talk about Accelerating the Enterprise Devops Journey (but don&amp;rsquo;t worry this will include an overview of Chef).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>